[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is false about learning according to Gagne's definition?",
    "options": [
      "It is a change in human disposition",
      "It persists over a period of time",
      "It is simply ascribable to processes of growth",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Manual or physical skills come under __________ component of Bloom's taxonomy.",
    "options": [
      "Cognitive",
      "Affective",
      "Psychomotor",
      "Physical"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Reflection, learning and education was explored by",
    "options": [
      "Carl Rogers",
      "John Watson",
      "Benjamin Bloom",
      "John Dewey"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The principles of __________ refer to how close in time two events must be for a bond to be formed.",
    "options": [
      "behavior",
      "reinforcement",
      "repetition",
      "contiguity"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "__________ gives information to learners about their success or failure concerning the task at hand.",
    "options": [
      "Cognitive feedback",
      "Emotional feedback",
      "Reinforcement",
      "Physical feedback"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The __________ orientation to learning has a quality of personal involvement-the whole person in both feeling and cognitive aspects being in the learning event.",
    "options": [
      "behavioral",
      "cognitive",
      "humanistic",
      "social"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Learning through play is __________ learning.",
    "options": [
      "primary",
      "secondary",
      "passive",
      "active"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "People with __________ learning style are prone to sorting their ideas after speaking, rather than thinking ideas through before.",
    "options": [
      "logical",
      "solitary",
      "visual",
      "auditory"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which of the following statements is false?",
    "options": [
      "Effective instruction is static",
      "Effective instruction is eclectic",
      "Effective instruction is generative",
      "Effective instruction is interactive"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "In ADDIE model, I stand for",
    "options": [
      "instruction",
      "implementation",
      "integration",
      "induction"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]